Namaste and welcome to this exciting episode of Sattology debunking mythology.
Sattology means science of truth or study of truth.
Opposite of that is mythology which means science or study of fake lie or imagination.
Sattology is made of two words Sat and Logo.
Sat is Sanskrit root word for Sat-Chit-Anand, truth.
And opposite of that is the myth, which
is also Sanskrit root word for fake lie or imagination.
So combined with logos, it becomes
Satology versus Mythology.
[SPEAKING HINDI]
So, let us welcome Professor Rameshwar Mishra Pankaj.
Today's topic is a very interesting topic and people talk about it again and again.
So first I will touch on history a little bit.
Even today, people call America, even though the settlers are Native American,
people still call this country a Judeo-Christian country.
and everyone accepts it,
whereas their population is only 45%.
Only 45%.
The majority of people in America are agnostic,
they call themselves atheists,
and if you say atheists,
it has a different connotation,
but they say that they are not affiliated with any religion.
And America calls itself a constitutional republic,
not a democracy.
Constitutional Republic is the idea of Aristotle, which is a little different from his Guru,
different from Geocraty and Plato.
So, in India, it is said that we are secular.
If someone reads the word secular in America, he thinks that they are atheists.
This is what the Americans think.
And that is why the image of Indians has been created in America or in the world of the empire,
that they are atheists.
That's why it can be easily converted.
But Indian politicians, academicians or Indian citizens never contest this.
They say that we are not secular.
And the left makes it a kind of a curse that these people are right wing fanatics.
So the right wing fanatics of America are Christians, whose name is Christian country.
But India's right wing is a minority, even though it is a majority, and the left wing which is called secular is prominent.
Do you think that is why the Indian government ignores the Hindu struggle?
No, there are two different things. First, why do we ignore the struggle of Hindus? We will talk about this later.
First, why is this state system in India?
So, what happened was that Netaji Subhash Chandra Bose was with Japan and Germany
and he had declared Independent India in 1943.
Swaraj and Swadesh were the two islands, he had a flag on them, a coin, a flag.
The minimum requirement for a sovereign state was fulfilled by the Britishers.
They had coins, national flag, national anthem.
They said that all these Indian territories are ours and the Britishers living here are strangers and outsiders.
They are outsiders and strangers.
They have no rights and it is our birthright to expel them.
But Germany was winning earlier, but later, for example, the Soviet army started beating Germany in many places, America came, it killed Japan, and the Indian soldiers protected the British soldiers in many places.
But before winning, they made a deal with Nehru and Gandhi ji, especially on Nehru's side, that we are very loyal, loyal because Jawaharlal Nehru had written a document.
The transfer of power document is from the British Maharani Press. In that, in many sections, the transfer of power documents are written clearly that Jawaharlal has suggested that the soldiers should be trained and they should be given guerilla training.
and they will go to fight Subhash Ghosh in the French of Kohima.
So when a person went so far that he was ready to give the support of the British to fight against his own country's hero,
then the British thought that this is our truth and we should transfer the power to it.
Because after transferring the power, they started doing it from 1917, they were scared of the first world war.
So, he was in search of a solution.
Till then Lokmanya Tilak, Lala Lajpat Rai, Bipin Chandra Pal, Raj Pihari Bose were there.
There were many patriots.
Till then he thought that whatever has been made by us, we will spoil it.
So, he was waiting.
So, he told Gandhi ji from South Africa that you are a pacifist, you are on our side, so let's go to India and do politics.
So, Gandhi ji was brought from South Africa and slowly, Motilal Nehru and Gandhi ji became a big lobby.
And later, they made Jawaharlal Nehru the President, who had no interest in politics and no understanding.
So, seeing Jawaharlal Nehru's loyalty to the British Crown, he was transferred and empowered.
So, what they did was that they made the India Act 1935 the base for the document.
And the officer at that time, who was Rao, D.S. Rao or B.S. Rao,
the Rao's who prepared the India Act 1935 draft of 1935,
they were given the responsibility to make the constitution of India.
And to show that, they made a committee of the whole world.
So, this is how the government was brought in.
But still, at that time, the people of India were under so much pressure that they neither called the government of India secular nor socialist.
They called it the Sovereign Republic.
After this, when Lal Bahadur Shastri was forced to negotiate with Pakistan on the orders of the leaders of the Soviet Union in the Tashkent,
and then it felt that he should not go and go back from here, so he was killed there.
Lal Bahadur Shastri ji, whose cause is being investigated, but has not been investigated yet.
So after that, on the signal of the Soviet Union, Indira Gandhi was made the Prime Minister of India
and after that the communists took over India.
the Indira Gandhi's arrival. 1969 onwards. So, what happened with this is that the communist dominated state started to run. So, they, Indira Gandhi was very corrupt, very corrupt, corrupted and was arbitrary and the suffering of the people was increasing.
So, the movement of Jai Prakash Narayan started, which he called the Total Revolution Movement.
So, he put an emergency because he was scared of it.
And in the emergency, he put the threat of communists and on the orders of the communists, he amended the constitution.
And the sovereign democratic republic was made into a secular socialist democratic republic.
When was India made secular? In 1975 when there was no democracy, no republic.
Now the whole context of secularism is Christianity.
When the Christian Churches did not fight among themselves, it was said that the state will remain secular.
But no society is secular. But in any major Christian nation in the world, secularism is not an adjective of state.
England is not a secular state, France is not a secular state, Germany is not a secular state, Holland, Netherlands, Spain, Portugal are not secular states.
and USA is not a secular state, they are all religious states.
And communist is also not a secular state,
that means USSR was not a secular state and China was not a secular state.
So it means that purposefully it was kept secular to bring it against Hinduism.
We are seeing the proof of this in Kerala, we will go into details there.
I will add one thing, in American constitution, American government can't directly donate to any church.
But what they have done is, they have made organizations in between, through which they donate to Christians.
I will give you an idea, around 70 billion dollars, which was given to Christian organizations only during Covid indirectly.
directly Indian government, American government didn't give, they gave through vehicles
and Islamic organizations in America, were given 7 to 8 billion dollars donation
but Hindu organizations were not given
and Hindus were also given indirectly, but all of them, none of them are directly connected to Hinduism
they were given only 1 or 2 billion dollars, but all of them are from social service organizations
There is no religion in that but rest of the groups are religious groups.
In this sense, you are saying a very important thing, but if I go into each and every branch, I may get lost in the subject, but let me say this.
The problem is that everyone knew who the Hindu was in Sanatan Dharma.
Vedas are the main branch of Sanatan Dharma, apart from this, the Buddhists, Jains and later on the Sikhs, who believe in some or the other Panth,
i.e. the fruit of Karma and rebirth, every Karma has a possible fruit and it is reversed, it is rebirth,
This was the condition.
So, these people who are secular or who do not believe in religion are not Hindus.
But later, the RSS people got an inferiority that they made a world Hindu parishad
and in that they convinced some saints and gave a strange definition which was never there in India
that anyone who is born in a Hindu family and if he has not renounced Hinduism, then he is a Hindu.
So, in this way, any communist, atheist, or any other religion who criticizes Hinduism, who abuses Vedas, who abuses Krishna,
who criticizes Jainism, who criticizes Buddhism, who does not even believe in Sikhs,
and those who do not believe in any religion and say that religion is all fake, that too is called Hindu.
This definition in Sanskrit is called "Svatovyahat" meaning "the one who breaks himself".
This means that the one who believes in Hindu religion and the one who works for the destruction of Hindu religion,
both are called Hindu by the Vishwa Hindu Parishad.
because they had an inferiority that everything happens with numbers.
So we increase our number.
And the situation is that the number of Muslims was very low after the partition,
but Muslims are dominating Indian politics.
The number of Christians was very low, but Christians are dominating.
So the number theory is clearly visible.
There were very few communists.
There are very few communists in India.
And they are dominating politics.
So what does the number mean?
and the one who destroys religion in the name of his number is also a Hindu and the one who follows religion is also a Hindu.
So this is the peak of foolishness.
Which was not there anywhere till 15th August 1947.
It was that the livelihood of the lier and the atheist will be given the right of life.
But he will not be considered a religious person and a Hindu.
He is not a Hindu, he will be called a lier.
But the Vishwa Hindu Parishad gave a strange explanation of Hindutva due to their ignorance and ignorance.
So, one thing happened, they called both the destroyer of religion and the follower of religion as Hindus.
And here the state, during Indira Gandhi's time, the communists took over completely.
The result is that even in the name of Hindutva, like we will give to Muslims, to Christians,
So, the Hindus should also be given some funds by the government.
So, they have chosen the organizations that are against Hinduism and are against the destruction of Hinduism.
But since they were called Hindus according to the definition of the Vishwa Hindu Parishad, they were given money.
That is, to spread Islam, they are giving money to Muslims through the consolidated fund of India.
The government treasury of India is used to fund the education of Islam and Christianity.
The consolidated fund of India, which is made up of the tax of Hindus,
is not used to fund the education of Hinduism.
On top of that, the atheists are also being funded in the name of Hinduism.
So this situation was created by the state. This situation was not even there in 15 August 1947.
So this is a very serious situation.
And what is happening because of this is that people are openly working against Hinduism.
But there is more to it.
And this is called false propaganda.
How does it work?
Now, there is a problem in this.
The religious, learned, knowledgeable, intelligent Hindus did not form a party.
Swami Karpatri ji did, but he was not aware of modern politics.
So, he was caught in his innocence.
There is a separate story about this.
It will take a long time to explain, so I will not tell you.
They were cheated. They were not allowed to succeed.
In the beginning, they had a very big impact on North India.
And after this, no religious, knowledgeable Hindu party was formed.
The party that was formed, it was RSS.
Because it was emerging as a force, it seemed that there were a lot of people in it.
During the partition, its branches started to grow.
Nehru, fearing that it would be a big power, banned it in the name of Gandhi's murder.
And then he suppressed it a lot.
You will see how Nehru killed Hindus in the name of Gandhi's murder.
But the main thing is that when RSS was banned, they created a party out of fear.
But in that party, no talk of protecting Hinduism was said.
because they were not religious and educated people. They were people who were working with the intention of gathering Hindus in the Sangh.
They did not have knowledge of religion, modern politics, so they did not talk about religion.
The result is that they did not have any knowledge of politics. We give two proofs of this.
There are many proofs, 50. First, according to any definition of religion, Gandhi cannot be called a non-violent.
And Gandhi himself is not a non-violent. How is he not? Gandhi wrote in both Harijan and Young India,
and he said that his definition of non-violence is not the one in Europe,
because non-killing is not non-violence,
but the definition of non-violence in Patanjali's Yog Sutra is what I believe.
So what is that definition?
"Sarvada Sarvatha Sarva-bhuteshu Anabhidroha Ahimsa"
"Sada Purna-tah Samast Praniyo Aur Pratitya Ke Tatvo Ke Prati Droha Ka Bhav"
"Maitri Ki Bhav Na Kaho Na Hi Ahimsa"
What is said about violence?
Vitarka himsa-adayah krita-karita-anumodita lobha-krodha-moha-purvaka mridu-madhyaadhimatra duhkha-ajnana-ananta-phala iti pratipaksa-bhavanam
There are three types of violence.
1. Krit, done by oneself.
2. Karai, done by others.
3. Anmodan, done by others.
These are the three types of violence.
After this, we have a deep analysis of everything here.
After that, it was said that it can be due to three reasons.
Greed, anger or lust.
Then it was said that there will be three more parts of it.
Soft, medium or extreme.
Soft, medium and extreme.
So, there are 81 types of violence.
So, according to that definition, Gandhi ji will be called violent.
because he killed Hindus by saying that poor Muslims were killing Hindus.
There was a riot in Moplah after the failure of the Khalifat movement.
So, the Moplahs killed Hindus there.
Gandhiji gave him such a way that he teaches them their religion, that he is a poor brother.
So, what is this?
krita-karita-anumodita
Gandhi ji himself did not kill the Hindus in Mopla, Kerala, but he got them killed and then he made them pay for it.
After this, in the partition, it was known that many people would die. Gandhi himself told Viceroy that "Let there be bloodbath."
The collected work of Mahatma Gandhi is there. I have given his page in my book.
Let there be bloodbath.
He knew that there will be bloodbath in large numbers.
Then why didn't you arrange for the protection of Hindus?
So what is this? They are violent. Gandhi ji is not violent in any way.
And all the poets of the Sangh started saying that Gandhi ji's violence is very bad.
Then like fools, they started writing stories and writing articles that India has not been subdued by non-violence.
And then they imagined that this king was also a non-violent person.
And that Brihadrath was a non-violent person.
And that Sumitra Shung removed him.
False stories.
False stories in the name of history.
And not knowing what is right for a person.
You could have called Gandhiji a non-violent person.
You could have said that you talk about non-violence in war, but your actions are violent according to the scriptures, because you have made violence, it is done and tolerated.
I am telling you how much ignorance.
Second, Jawaharlal Nehru wrote a letter to Gandhiji that war is going to happen soon in the world.
This was written when the Second World War had started and the Soviet Union was being attacked.
That soon there will be bloodshed in the world and at that time I will be with the communist party and the Soviet Union.
class war and class struggle. This is Jawaharlal Nehru's letter to Gandhi. So how did he become a pacifist? The one who is saying that the fire of violence will ignite, there will be a struggle and I will support the Soviet Union.
So, the Soviet Union made a plan that the subordinates of the Soviet bloc, the nation-states, will not keep an army.
They will talk about peace and if they face any problem, we will defend them.
So, they made a peace army everywhere.
This is a proposal of the Soviet Union, a communist international.
So, on the signal of the communist international, Jawaharlal Nehru talked about peace here.
The Sangh people said that he is a pacifist.
You give your enemy the wrong idea.
You consider Gandhi as a non-voilent and Jawaharlal Nehru as a pacifist.
This shows that he does not have political sense.
Either he is a joint devotee of Gandhi, which I do not see.
If we assume that he has political sense,
then he will be accused of being an agent of Gandhi and Jawaharlal Nehru.
or they had collusion, so I don't believe it.
That's why I'm saying that they are ignorant.
Now, the Maoist party attacked Tibet.
Jawaharlal Nehru stated in the parliament
that the Chinese soldiers are in great trouble,
so we are sending them rice,
we are sending them RATIONS,
and some soldiers as well.
That is, he sent an army and sent food.
For whom?
Because they could not capture Tibet.
Neither were they familiar with the climate there, nor the mountains there.
So they never captured Tibet.
Jawaharlal Nehru sent the Indian army and guided them to go from here and there.
And they captured Tibet.
At that time, Lohia called Nehru a traitor.
But the Sangh never said.
They say, "No, no, they are peaceful people and they are innocent."
So, these people are foolish.
Or they are very oppressed.
The result is that even after coming to power,
they did not remove the word "socialist" and "secularist" that were used in the emergency.
But it is not just about this.
Now, let's come to your main question.
Why are Hindus being killed and why do they do this?
Jawaharlal Nehru was clear that he wanted to bring communist rule in India, but he was a bit smart.
He thought that he would not murder like Stalin.
One reason for this was that the caste system in India was very strong.
And that was a blessing for us, our strength.
So, because of the caste system, if you kill some people of a particular caste, then the rest of the people of that caste will take revenge on you.
This is true till 15th August 1947.
Because people of all the castes of India were warriors.
In the army, people of all the castes of India were in the army.
All of them, Raman, Kshatriya, Vaishya and the ones who are called Shudras, they all were in the army.
You see, during Janak's time, all kinds of armies were there.
So, all the people of India are warriors, soldiers, and soldiers.
If you kill their people, they will kill you.
In Russia, the farmer was poor.
He was poor since the time of Jarr.
So, when the communists made the farmers laborers,
through collectivization of agriculture,
they took away the farms of the farmers.
They couldn't do anything.
If the farms were taken away in India, there would have been a murder.
So, Jawaharlal Nehru was very smart.
He thought he would slowly get the check-bonding done and do a lot of such things.
He said about cooperative farming.
He was bringing communism slowly.
So, that's why he got him killed.
Then he considered RSS as his enemy.
As soon as he heard about Gandhi's murder, he let it go.
In a way, indirectly permitted that Gandhi may be murdered.
There were attemp of murdering Gandhi earlier as well
Jawaharlal knew about it.
And he killed those people later.
So, the secret police did not follow them and did not try to catch them.
This means that Gandhi was allowed to be killed by Jawaharlal Nehru.
Let there be the murder of Mahatma Gandhi.
because he was coming in their way.
So, he was in this state.
The next day, without any proof, without any FIR,
he was given the RSS, Savarkar, Hindu Mahasabha.
And then in Maharashtra and in some parts of Gujarat
and in some parts of Madhya Pradesh, like at the house of Biryan Kumar Saklecha,
So, he killed the Brahmins and other Hindus who supported the Sangh.
He made stone in their houses, used sticks, set fire.
This is how he killed the Hindus.
In return for Gandhi's murder, Jawaharlal Nehru, or his government, if he cannot be called personal,
his party members killed the Hindus.
After this, Hindus were killed in Kashmir, we all know.
After this, in Bengal, Hindus are being killed, and the Indian Jantar Party's own activists are being killed.
They don't say anything. In Assam, Nagaland, Hindus were killed, and then slowly, slowly, they were converted into Christians.
Now, Nagaland, Manipur, and Meghalaya are not secular states, they are religious states. They are Christian states.
De facto. Nagaland, Meghalaya, Manipur, Manipur is not yet done and Mizoram.
Nagaland, Meghalaya and Mizoram, they are de facto Christian state.
They are not secular state. But Indian government is still secular.
And the bigger thing is, now we have to see what is their problem,
but the bigger thing is that the people who are important in our constitution,
In the emergency, Indira Gandhi had made a very strong point that the fundamental duties of Indian citizens are in Article 51 of the Constitution.
It is good that they will work to protect the unity and integrity of the country.
They will work for sovereignty and integrity of their country.
If it is said that they will work for the protection of the country, then they will work for the protection of the country.
But the 51(e) which is called A, B, C, D, 51(d) means the part of Constitution 4(a)
Article 51(d) says that to promote harmony and the spirit of common brotherhood amongst
all the people of India transcending religious, linguistic and regional or sectional diversities.
Common brotherhood is the fundamental duty of every citizen.
So when in India, a Christian preacher or a Muslim propagandist publicly says that your God is weak, Krishna is weak, Christ is powerful or your Ram and Krishna are weak,
It is a disgrace to Krishna's and Rama's character.
And our Allah is powerful.
So what is this doing?
This is the fundamental duty to promote brotherhood.
It is obstructing that.
And if any Indian citizen obstructs brotherhood,
obstructs it, puts obstacles in it,
then he is violating the fundamental duty.
The basic duty of an Indian citizen is being violated.
So, his citizenship should be terminated.
So, if anyone in India says that only Christian religions are superior,
Hinduism is inferior, Hindu gods and goddesses are inferior,
and Hinduism is criticized by Hindu scriptures,
then at the same time, his citizenship should be taken away.
He is not eligible to be a citizen of India because he violates Article 51, which is the fundamental duty of an Indian citizen.
But state did nothing.
He went to Kerala and Bengal and in the whole country, Muslim and Christian propagandists publicly say that Hindu religion is inferior, Hindu gods are bad, their character is bad.
and they permit this.
So, in this way, the rulers of India
are violating the constitution of India.
Because the fundamental duties
of the citizens who do not do these duties should be abolished.
So, why are these BJP people not protecting the citizens of India?
Why are they not protecting brotherhood, the feeling of brotherhood, the feeling of brotherhood?
Instead of that, for the majority of the Indian society, spreading hatred, malice, and malice is public.
This is all public in India.
So this is a terrible thing, isn't it?
So why are they doing this?
The BJP and RSS people should tell us.
But the question is, are there at least 100 crore Hindus in India,
and there is no group of educated, well-educated, religiously knowledgeable,
enlightened Hindus, who can form a Hindu party?
We must follow this constitution, because the BJP government is violating Article 51 of this constitution.
Congress has done it, now the BJP is doing it.
Where is the common brotherhood?
As soon as you abuse other's religion, other's deity, then communal brotherhood is over.
You are violating article 51.
I don't know why they don't do it, but they are doing it continuously.
This means that their...
...equality of religions is not pure.
Giving prominence to Hindu religion is a different matter.
Right?
Giving importance to Hindu religion, we don't know when it will come.
Hinduism does not consider Islam and Christianity equal. Instead, it gives funds to both.
And the Hindus who are atheists, i.e. the things which are not Hindu,
initially, Vishwendu Parishad called them Hindus by using a false definition.
Because a socialist and Marxist cannot be a Hindu by any definition.
The one who talks about eating cow meat cannot be a Hindu by any definition.
The British have a record of the Gauraksha movement from 1890 to 1900. I have written a book on the history of India in the India Office Library.
The British Queen has written in the book that the Gauraksha movement is a movement of awakening of Hindus and that we will be driven out of India.
Why? Because on the question of cow protection Arya Samajis, Murthy Pujars, Sanatan Dharmis, Sikhs, Jains, Buddhists, all are one.
This is the letter of Queen Victoria to the Viceroy.
Cow protection is a principle in which Sikhs, Jains, Buddhists, Sanatan Dharmis and Arya Samajis are all one.
This is a very big issue.
BJP has not even raised such a big issue.
Jawaharlal was a Hindu traitor.
But BJP claims that he is a Hindu.
And they bring foreign currency from Gaumansk.
This is a great sin.
The government that takes money from Gaumansk is a sinner.
According to the Indian scriptures.
This is a great sin.
What do you do with foreign currency from the government?
You reduce your expenses, ask from the people of India.
Chanakya has said that if the government needs it, it should ask the citizens for it.
The word 'pranay' has a meaning of 'gain' but he said that we should ask for more money.
If you are honest and cut down on your expenses,
not that the government should spend endlessly and ask the citizens for money.
If you are simple minded, from Prime Minister to Minister, to Chief Minister to Apsar, you should be simple minded, with less expenditure and then you can ask for money from citizens and they will give you.
But if you are selling cow meat and taking money, then you are a great sinner.
In 16th century I remember a conversation between Chaitanya Mahaprabhu and Kazi written by Krishnadas Goswami.
I have not read all the Vedas carefully and I don't have quotations.
Many viewers have quotations.
Chaitanya Mahaprabhu says that killing cows is not a part of Vedas.
It is not written anywhere.
But some Rig Vedic people who have a communist mindset have translated it wrongly.
People have misunderstood that in Vedas also people ate cow meat, even Indra ate cow meat.
No, but in that, the sense of authority is important.
One should decide who is whose authority.
If I say that the one who is murdered is a communist, then will they accept that he is a communist?
Yes, that is the right logic.
If I am not an authority about communism, then how can any Christian be an authority about the Vedas?
Communist is not an authority, he is an unauthorised person, he must be punished, he or she.
So, it is the duty of the Indian government to punish those who misinterpret the Vedas.
In many Vedas, it is said, in the Merik book, all the principles are there, the principles of Sanskrit, Kashmita, Goma, etc.
Those who lie about the Vedas, about the scriptures, they are criminals, not punishable, but criminals.
And this is also according to this, they condemn the common brotherhood.
So, even this constitution can punish if the government's intention is good.
I believe that the intention of the Sangh, BJP and Modi Ji is not good.
And if the intention is good, then he is a coward.
And see, the coward has been condemned a lot here.
You have read Mahabharata.
What does Vidula say to his son?
When he comes back from the battlefield, he says that the coward is not a son.
He is a 'Purish' meaning a 'Mutra' (a male)
This is in Mahabharata. If a prince is a 'Kair' then he is a 'Mutra' not a 'Putra' (a male)
He has also come out of the 'Yoni' path and 'Mutra' also comes out. So, he is not a 'Putra' but a 'Mutra'
So, this is the standard of India. If a ruler is a 'Kair' then he is a 'Mutra'
Then he is not a human being.
Why are they afraid? Why are they afraid of following the constitution? Why are they afraid of following the constitution?
We will have to see. Why are they afraid of protecting Hindu Dharma?
The rest are not afraid of correcting their enemies. They are afraid of protecting Hindu Dharma.
So, they should decide for themselves. I have already told you what is Mahabharata.
No, it is a very low feeling. Always looking at others, not understanding about yourself.
One should take inspiration from others but for that also we need to have a character.
What kind of character? Is it good or bad?
And in Bhagwat Purana the definition is very clear.
Those who believe in Vedas are the religious. Those who are against Vedas are not religious.
But Vedas are a book of...
It is a book of the world which defines a common law.
It is a golden standard.
You will attain salvation only by approaching it.
If you go against it, you will go away from salvation.
But any government...
We are talking about the social level.
But no Indian government in the world talks about Sanatan Dharma on the basis of Vedas.
They talk about Sanatan Dharma with the mindset of secularism, with the mindset of Aristotle.
He is a Greek philosopher and Yavan is our Shastra.
We are translating it through the medium of Yavan in today's common law.
So, there will be unrest in that.
One last question, we have seen many Hindu leaders who call themselves Hindu leaders, they talk about this.
The attacks against Hindus are happening everywhere, in Bengal, Kerala, people don't tell but it is happening in Karnataka, Uttar Pradesh, Madhya Pradesh.
is happening there as well and nobody is talking about it. Media is not aware of it and you
are right that such people should be punished. So, what should such people do in today's
society, what should youth do, so that they do not have to suffer so much of 'Avahilna'
What should people do, what should youth do in today's society,
that they don't have to suffer so much of 'Avahilna'
because all the laws, a little Hindu youth will be awakened,
he is shut down in SC/ST Act. I have heard it many times from people.
I don't live in India, but I have heard it.
So what should such a youth do?
No, we will have to try in many ways.
The most powerful person in the world,
is not an inspiration to make a political party.
If he is not, then Owesi has called its Muslim youth
to become a constitutional expert.
While in reality, this constitution instructs to control Islam.
In the constitution it is written to control everything that attacks the majority.
So, Hindus or people who are sitting in America or anywhere,
Read this constitution carefully.
As I said, there are many reasons for which the government is responsible for protecting Hindu religion.
And there is no reason to suppress the majority religion in the world in democracy.
And this was not even in the constitution.
Congress has misinterpreted it and made it arbitrary.
So, first of all, the people of the Sangh/RSS-BJP
say that the constitution is wrong.
And after that, they even pay homage to the constitution.
This constitution is like this.
And then when you reach the door of the parliament,
you pay homage to the constitution.
You pay homage to that parliament,
and on the other hand, you also pay homage to Gandhi ji.
which Gandhi ji used to call 'Vishya' and 'Bandh'.
So, the main thing is that it is anarchy, materialism is uncivilized and thought is virtuous.
So, the people sitting outside, especially those who are outside,
they should first awaken their materialism, practice wisdom.
If possible, make a learning center like this, which studies and trains people on Indian politics.
I have been saying this for many years, it should be a knowledge center.
There should be 1-2 such centres where it is told what is happening in the world, what is happening in India and how wrong it is.
One more point here, we will have to do publicity, so that we have truth in propaganda too.
Now we should not say that we will have to improve the language.
Like I do not agree with the fact that they are inspired by foreigners and look at other's faces. Not at all.
They intentionally do what makes them inferior, what they call 'Yogai Bhuma Tatsukam' which is great, great, big, this is inferiority.
How? What inspiration do they get from England?
In England, the crown is the official legal patron of the Protestant Church.
So, you take inspiration from England, brother.
and the English language is the majority language of the British Empire,
so how did you get inspired by England?
Neither did you give official legal protection to the majority religion,
nor did you patronize it,
whereas the English crown is the official legal patron of the Protestant Church.
Nor did you make the Indian language Sanskrit.
If you leave Hindi, then develop a language in which Hindi, Marathi, Bangla, Tamil, Gujarati, all have common words.
Develop such a language, work a little.
So do something for India, they are not even copying the countries of the world, so you cannot say that they are inspiring.
Now see, why don't you get inspired from America?
You can get inspired from America by the government's farm, or you can get inspired by England.
So the president should have an official legal pattern of Hindu religion.
Because there is an official legal pattern of the Crown Protestant Church.
Or if you take America, when the president changes in America, the whole secretariat changes.
So this bureaucracy should not have so much power that it keeps changing the leaders.
Suppose they want to be secular in any sense, then they should make at least three parishes.
First of all, they should make a great parish of Sanatan Dharma and give it official recognition.
Second, they should say that since another country has been formed in the name of Islam,
then it is necessary to make something called Indian Islam.
Third, make India a Church of India. If this is the case, like the king of England made the Church of England,
apart from the Pope, so he says that there will be a Church of England and any Christian in India will have to show allegiance to the Church of India.
So it will be in their control. You make a Church of India, make a Sanatan Dharma Mahaparishad and tell the Muslims that India will be a Mahaparishad of Muslims.
There should be some control of the government. You are not secular in that sense either.
And the fund thing was very important.
Churches are still funded by the Government of India and all the state governments.
In the name of relief to the whole world.
So, they fund churches, they fund Muslim organizations.
So, they are not secular, they are not religious, they are people who spread arbitrariness and anarchy.
We have to say something against them.
So, people in America and abroad should say the truth.
It is not necessary that you are politically aggressive.
But, create learning centres in a very peaceful manner.
Spread the truth from there that what is happening.
India is not as unjust as India is.
So, we have to adopt a strategy in many ways.
I would say to them to make a Church of India.
So, all the Christians in India will be loyal to Church of India.
It cannot be against England.
It cannot be against Sweden or America.
Everyone will have to register as Church of India.
There will be control. In India, there are American, English, Scottish, Welsh and Switzerland churches. There are 50 churches working together. What is happening? Or you can say that this is an open field, let the Hindus also play.
Actually the concept of nation state is bad.
The concept of nation state is a European concept.
We will do another show on this.
India is being called a civilizational state.
People are not understanding this.
They are saying something new.
In English it is called civilization.
It is a phrase.
In the world, there is no place where phraseology is used to run politics.
Phraseology is a cover for politics.
This means that the people who are saying this, we will talk about it next time,
they are covering something.
They are hiding something. Because this is phraseology.
They have never defined what is civilizational state.
If that is the case, then say that it is a Hindu nation, civilization is Hindu.
They don't have honesty.
They have no interest in the civilizational state. They are coining phrasers.
The phrasiology is being played by the leaders of India since 1947.
Nehru did it, Indira did it, remove poverty.
Now their grandson says that poverty has not been removed yet.
There should be some rule of law that if the party that announces,
if it does not follow it, then its people should be compensated for every loss.
So, it should be compensated and punished.
Rahul Gandhi can be blamed for this only if India does the right thing
that your party said to remove poverty, why are you still talking about poverty?
This is a criminal offence because you are deceiving, you are betraying and disowning your party's manifesto.
But the one who does it should be the ruler, not the ruler.
The problem is that BJP's rule is the rule of cowards.
Look, people will believe it is bad but I am a Brahmin and my job is to speak the truth.
BJP's rule is the rule of cowards. That's why all his thoughts are futile.
He will not get any result.
So, leave aside Klaibyu, there should be someone who can say Klaibyam Maasam Gamah Bharat.
There should be someone who can say Klaibyam Maasam Gamah Narendra Modi.
This is an example of atheism that they will make a different version of Cleibhiv.
They will say Cleibhiv means not to steal. The basic meaning is to be unknowing.
It literally means, you are telling me on the basis of Sanskrit, it literally means to shrink.
It also has the meaning that if a man's senses shrink then he cannot do anything.
But there it is not saying Arjuna in that sense because his senses were not shrinking.
The mind is restricted and the body is not.
Our Shashaks are restricted by mind and intellect.
It is possible that body is very hungry and lustful but mind and intellect are restricted.
So, we should awaken the power in mind and intellect.
Body has a lot of power but mind and intellect does not.
In Sanskrit, the word 'Klab' means 'concentrated' or 'concentrated' in Sanskrit.
So physical napunjak is different from mental and physical napunjak.
Krishna knows what kind of a person Arjuna is, so he won't say anything.
It means something else, because he is different.
Arjuna was not hijara or impotent. He was showing his mind and intellect at that time. His mind was shrinking or going into klyva state.
Thank you so much Rameshwar ji. People who are watching, please subscribe, like and share widely.
This is such an important conversation. In this, each point that Rameshwar ji has said, there is deep research, there is a book.
And send me the link of your book. If there is any link, I will share it with everyone.
And if everyone gets the links of his books in the community notes, then you can buy and read it.
And the book that he wrote on cows, I am going to buy it myself quickly.
I want to see Vedic references and use them.
Thank you very much.
It was published by Sitaram Goyal ji in the book 'Biblia Impacts - Viceroyalty of India'
She had published it herself.
She had read it through and through.
If you don't know about Sitaram Goyal ji, you can search about her and you will know who she is.
He is considered as a great Hindu and he has done many kind of researches.
And also in our tradition, many of our Acharyas like Chaitanya Mahaprabhu, Madhavacharya, Ramamrithacharya,
who are the people of tradition, they also have such writings. You can read them also.
There are many good scholars in Shankaracharyas.
Like Shankaracharya of 143rd Govardhan Math and other Shankaracharyas of Kanchi Math.
And many of their great sons and great grandsons have come to our show.
You can read them too. There are many books.
Thank you very much. Namaste. We will meet again in the next show.
Namaste.